<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- SIGN UP PROMPT -->
    <string name="sign_up_prompt_trainer_title">Also a Pet Trainer?</string>
    <string name="sign_up_prompt_trainer_message">Are you also registered as a Pet Trainer On Zen Pets? If you are registered as a Pet Trainer on Zen Pets, you get an awesome 25% discount on your annual charges.
        \n\nTo get the discount, click \"YES\". If you are a Pet Trainer, but haven\'t registered yet, you will still get the discount from the Pet Trainer\'s application.
        \n\nIf you are not a Pet Trainer or haven\'t registered yet, click \"CONTINUE\"
        \n\nNOTE: Make sure you use the same email address as the one used for the Pet Trainer\'s account.</string>
    <string name="sign_up_prompt_trainer_yes">YES</string>
    <string name="sign_up_prompt_trainer_no">CONTINUE</string>

    <!-- TRAINER FAILED ERROR PROMPT -->
    <string name="trainer_failed_title">No Trainer found</string>
    <string name="trainer_failed_message">No Pet Trainer\'s account with the specified email address was found. To try again, check the email address provided and click \"TRY AGAIN\".
        \n\nIf you had chosen \"YES\" on the previous screen accidentally, press \"CONTINUE\" to pay the annual charges and create your new account.
        \n\nNOTE: You will be provided the 25% discount when you register for a Pet Trainers account with the same email address</string>
    <string name="trainer_failed_try_again">TRY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="trainer_failed_continue">CONTINUE</string>

    <!-- PAYMENT FAILED -->
    <string name="payment_failed_title">Payment Failed</string>
    <string name="payment_failed_message">There was an error processing the payment. To try again, click the \"TRY AGAIN\" button. If the payment fails repeatedly, try a different payment method.</string>
    <string name="payment_failed_try_again">TRY AGAIN</string>
    <string name="payment_failed_cancel">CANCEL</string>

    <!-- LIMIT EXCEEDED -->
    <string name="kennel_limit_title">Kennel Listing Limit</string>
    <string name="kennel_limit_message">You have already listed two (2) Kennels using your account. A Kennel Owner can only publish two (2) Kennels per account.
        \n\nTo add additional Kennels, we recommend creating a new account on the Zen Pets Kennel Manager.</string>
    <string name="kennel_limit_okay">OKAY</string>
</resources>